In front of me are 10 YouTubers. And
starting now, two of them are traders.
>> Oh.
>> Oh my gosh.
>> All right.
>> Stick. Stake. Stick with me. Stick with
me.
>> You're my friend. Come on. Come on.
>> By the way, I'm not imposter. So stay
with me.
>> Jimmy, if you stay by me but kill
[music] me, I might just become an
imposter in real life if you do that.
>> I promise I'm not imposter. I'm not. I'm
not.
>> And if one of [music] the traders
manages to win, they get a real life
diamond sword. But for the eight of us,
we must complete tasks and get off this
island before [music] they murder us
all. Good luck.
>> Nick, you're my buddy. I trust you. I
trust you, dude. You want to go do
tasks? Let's do it.
>> All right, let's go. If I want that
sword, I'm going to have to manipulate
the entire lobby.
>> Uh,
Ryan, you wouldn't you wouldn't kill me
straight away, right?
>> Absolutely not, dude. What do we have to
do?
>> I see a check mark over here. So, I
think maybe going to check this out.
>> Okay, you're going to have to guide me,
okay? Please, if I'm your guide dog,
Ryan, you can't kill me.
>> Oh, that's a that's a fair deal.
[music]
>> Kitchen, maybe. Oh, this is this a task
I have to do.
>> Oh. Oh,
>> what happened?
>> Wait, did you walk through something?
Wait, how did you vent?
>> What do you mean?
>> HOW DID YOU VENT?
>> WHAT? I don't I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT
THIS IS.
>> NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
Oh my god.
Oh my gosh. Wait. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
Whoa. Whoa. What happened?
>> Wait. Somebody died.
>> No, I pressed the button. Ryan just
vented right in FRONT OF ME.
>> RYAN VENTED.
>> NO, I didn't. You vented.
>> Order. Or order in the court. Who
witnessed Ryan vent?
>> I saw a thousand witnessed Ryan 3000
vent right in front of me.
>> I thought it was a task. All right. I
thought I was helping.
>> Oh [laughter] no.
>> Crit task. Clean the vents.
>> I think Ryan's going to get voted out
here, but I have a plan. I can still win
this. I'm going to need to make these
guys not trust each other at all.
>> Okay, so I guess we all know who we're
voting for.
>> Yep.
>> All right, throw up the vote.
>> Spare me,
>> Ryan. I'm sorry.
>> I'm sorry, Ryan.
>> I was so excited. I wanted to get one
guy.
>> Goodbye, Ryan.
>> No.
>> Bye, Ryan.
>> All right, follow me. Follow me. Let's
do tasks.
>> Okay, bet.
>> I'll stick with you, Mr. Beast. Dream,
can you be honest with me?
>> Yeah.
>> Are you the murderer?
>> No, I'm actually not.
>> Okay. Okay. Me neither.
>> Everything okay over here, guys?
>> What's up, bro?
>> Okay. All right. I did my task.
>> Oh, wait. I got to do my task. Why is
there a dead cat? Oh, wait. Sleeping.
>> Hey, my task over here.
>> I have a task 44 me away. I need to kill
Dream. Dream's the smartest one here,
probably.
>> As the traitor, I have a bunch of
sabotages to help me.
Oh.
W.
Yo, come here. Come here. Come here.
Come here. I'm not trying to die. No.
No. No. No. No. Oh. Oh. Look out.
>> No. No. No. I'm actually scared of the
dark. It's okay. It's We're safe
together. We're safe together.
>> I'll hop in a vent and see if I can get
a kill.
>> No. But it's okay cuz we're safe
together, right? Are you sure? You're
not the murderer, right? No, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
Would you?
>> Oh my god. Maybe, maybe I killed him
right in front of him. I killed him
right in front of him. Hello.
>> Oh, wa.
>> Wait, what?
>> No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I I I
clicked on a dead body and then we all
got teleported here.
>> Wait, YOU SAW A DEAD BODY? WHERE?
>> Folton died. Folton died literally right
in front of me. We were both doing a
task. The lights went out and then he
just died instantly.
>> No,
>> that was an insane kill.
>> Who was nearby?
>> The only person I saw nearby
>> was Dream.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> How was I? I was Wait, how was I nearby?
I was nowhere nearby.
>> Okay, hold on. Listen. I was with Dream
with the lights turned off and he was
shooting a bow at targets.
>> What?
>> This is what I know. I went downstairs
outside like, you know, a minute before
the round ended. The last person I saw
when I was leaving, not there anyone in
the bus, but I did see Jimmy downstairs
when I left. Oh, okay.
>> Oh, I can assure you it's not me.
>> How?
>> And how is that?
>> I don't think it's Jimmy cuz he would
have killed me.
>> M. Okay. Okay. So, who's clear for this
kill?
>> Listen, me and Stake can clear each
other cuz we were with each other the
entire time. Like when the darkness went
out. Wait, wait, wait. So, sword, they
died while the lights were off. Okay.
So, Stake, me and you clear each other,
right? Cuz we we were near each other
the entire time. And that
>> Dream is talking too much.
>> He's trying so hard to clear him.
>> Yeah.
>> Who is unaccounted for when [music] the
lights were off?
>> Wait, wait. Abraham, where were you?
You've been quiet.
>> I was with with Jimi and Gr. [laughter]
>> I DON'T know if I believe that.
>> Yo, Nick, what's the accusation?
>> I don't know. I He's been quiet the
whole time. This is perfect. Nobody
suspects me.
>> Dude, where were you when the lights
went out
>> with uh I I was with Gra, Nick A30, and
Abraham, but I did branch off. I was
doing the firewood thing.
>> Then it's Jimmy. [music] Jimmy's the
only one that's only accounted for,
>> bro. I Yeah, I was with Rox and Jude. I
just I I was with multiple people.
>> What if we skip cuz it's so early in the
round and we we get a little more info.
>> Deal. So, we skip.
>> Guys, remember we still need to fix
lights after the meeting.
>> Uh-oh.
>> I'm with you. Swords. Sword. Swords.
>> Okay, Jimmy. Let's go. Let's go. Let's
go this way.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> St. Please don't be the imposter.
>> Please do not be the imposter.
>> Okay. Nick's over here. Hey, guys.
Should we just sit here and then if
there's a body, we know. While the boys
are bickering, I'm going to have some
Fastville's creamy peanut butter cups.
You already know these cups have real
peanut butter straight from a jar. Man,
they taste amazing.
>> We need to turn the lights on or
>> Okay, maybe we should go do lights.
>> Yeah, maybe we should all move towards
lights. I'm following Julo. I don't want
to go first, dude. I'm walking into the
abyss.
>> And not only does Fast taste amazing,
but we also ethically source our cacao.
You can buy some Fastables today at
these retailers.
>> All right, I'm alone right now.
>> Dude, I'm scared. This game is freaking
scary, dude. Okay, I think this confirms
it's Abraham. I think it's Abraham.
>> Wait, why do you think it's him?
>> Cuz I've cleared everyone else. You're
like the last person I've cleared and
then now it has to be Abraham.
>> Okay. Interesting. I think somebody's
about to die for sure. Like, should we
go fix the lights?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> All right. We're almost there. Okay.
Who's not here? Is Gro and
>> I'm going to do another task alone here
in the forest.
>> Hey. Yeah.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. Oh, okay. Okay,
they're back on.
>> Can we go check house? Cuz I have a test
in there as well.
>> Okay,
>> I've got a task over here as well that I
need to do.
>> Yeah, let's all five stay together. Just
let the other two mess up. And
>> where did you just come from? Where did
you come from?
>> Where did you just come from?
>> Hey, from the house. I was doing one
task.
>> That's pretty sus.
[music]
>> There's a vent. There's a vent. There's
a vent. There's a vent. There's a vent.
There's a vent. There's a vent.
>> Oh, he vented. He vented. He vented.
>> Oh, right here. Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Guys. Yo, he literally Yeah, he just
vented.
>> I knew you were being quiet in that
round. I knew it.
>> All right. Abraham vented.
>> Everyone, we saw Abraham vent.
>> Wait, Abraham vented?
>> Yeah. No, it's Abraham.
>> No, I I I didn't know you can do that.
[laughter]
>> Are you confirming you're the killer?
>> All right, throw up a vote.
>> No, I don't b I don't I I can't.
>> Oh, come on. I don't believe it.
>> Okay,
>> we got him framed.
>> I don't believe you.
>> It's It's Abraham. Let's vote him out.
>> No. Okay.
>> Bye.
>> All right. We win. We win.
>> Wait. What? Oh, wait. It was not him.
>> What? What? It wasn't him.
>> Oh, hell. What?
>> I feel really bad now. I thought it was
Abraham.
>> I thought we got that right. Everybody
voted for it.
>> Who is it then? IF IT'S NOT ABRAHAM, who
could it be?
>> How many tasks does everyone have? Cuz
I've got three bridge pieces. So, we can
>> I have two. Should we just go build?
>> I have two. Yeah. Let's Let's go to the
bridge.
>> We go one at a time to see how many
bridge pieces people have to see if
they're actually doing tasks.
>> Okay. I just put one down. So, I'll do
two, three. There you go.
>> I only have one, but I'm placing I have
one. That's it.
>> Wait a second. Jimmy. Jimmy. Jimmy, come
here for a sec. Come here for a sec. I
think it's Rem. I think it's Dream. He
immediately tried to get me to clear him
off rip.
>> Honestly, Dream's acting kind of sus,
too. Dream's the one who perpetuated the
whole Abraham vintage theory.
>> Let's just keep this between us for now
and observe and see what happens.
>> Yeah. Stake, bro. Stay. This is our
little secret. Okay.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I won't tell. Don't worry.
>> Okay. Bro, I have zero. Bro,
>> you've got zero bridge pieces. Okay. So,
wait. So,
uh-oh.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Someone
sabotaged. We don't know the names. We
don't know who's who. Oh, great. All
right, I got to kill someone here. I
have to kill someone here. [laughter]
>> OH, I'M RUNNING. I'M RUNNING.
>> This guy's running off alone.
>> Oh my gosh. Okay, I'm doing this. I'm
doing this. Is there someone with me? No
one is with me.
>> This guy's alone.
>> We'll have to wash off our disguises.
So, I saw steak go off in the other
direction.
>> I could kill him. I'm going to go.
>> Here we go. Okay, first half is gone.
>> 1 2 3 4.
>> Oh, there's another one. Dang. Oh, maybe
they went to that one. Actually, we'll
see. If Stake is not here doing this
task, like fixing the sabotage, well,
then we'll know he ran off trying to
look for a kill with someone else.
Oh, wait. WHAT? WHOA. Who's there? Who?
Okay. Wait, wait. Three people. Three
people together. Three people together.
>> I just arrived and reported the body.
>> There were three people in that pool
with the body and it was Dream. Me and
someone else. I got some valuable
information here. So, when the name
plates went off, I was keeping an eye on
Mr. Beast and Stake. And I saw Stake go
off to the right. There was someone else
though that went with Stake and it was
only one other person. So, if we can
clear people doing the task.
>> Wait, Sword. Who were you with us at the
end?
>> I went left when we came back from the
bridge and there was like an archery
thing. I'm pretty sure I thought it was
Jimmy [music] so I was following him cuz
I said I was sticking with him.
>> Then sword is pretty far from the body.
>> So sword is cleared. Sword is cleared.
>> Gro, where were you like the whole time?
>> I just ran to the side of the house on
the other side.
>> So the [music] right side.
>> Uh I don't even know which side I ran
on.
>> It's either Jude or Gro. And if if Jude
is being truthful, which I think he
would be saying that he was with me,
then it was then it wasn't Jude. I know
for a fact sword was on the left side
because I literally was over there
trying to shoot archery and I forgot you
can't [music] do tasks. So the fact that
he knew that sword was at archery. He
said it without me bringing it up proves
he is over there.
>> 100% certainty it's dude lower rocks. I
would bet my life on it. It's dude lower
rocks.
>> Okay. You said that last time and then
you got people killed. So I don't I
don't like that.
>> You're You know what? You're right,
dude. I'll take it back. Sword. It It
technically could be swords still, but
>> what?
>> All right. Well, hear me out, though.
Hear me out. Hear me out. Dream story is
literally not adding up. When I ran on
the bridge and I was like, "Guys, I have
big news." And Snake told me to be
quiet. It's because Snake pulled me
aside and said, "I can't clear Dream."
>> No, because he pushed so hard, but I'm
very sus OF HIM. OH,
>> WAIT. THAT'S WEIRD. Why is Jimmy lying?
Why is Jimmy lying? That's weird. He did
not say that.
>> Bro, I promise Snake said that. Why else
would I run up and go, "Guys, guys,
guys, guys." And then Snake told me to
be quiet. That's literally what he told
me.
>> Dream, you weren't on the left. There
was only three of us. I WAS ON THE LEFT.
I was
>> I think we vote Gro if not Grock's
dream. And honestly, if it's neither of
them, you can vote me out.
>> All right, I'm voting Dream. And
remember, after the vote, the sabotage
is going to reenable. I'm just going to
vote you Gro just to just to get relieve
some pressure off my shoulders.
>> I voted Gro as well,
>> bro. There is no way. OKAY, VOTE DREAM,
GUYS. GUYS, LISTEN TO ME RIGHT NOW. VOTE
DREAM.
>> OH MY GOD.
>> He's a liar. He's a liar.
Oh, okay. Oh, it's definitely Dream.
>> What? It's got to be Dream, then.
>> You know what? I'm just going to go sit
in the corner.
>> Oh my god, this is actually perfect.
Dream is next on the chopping block. We
have to kill Mr. Beast and blame it on
Dream.
Dream is staying completely out of the
map. So, the only two people left are
Jude and Nick A30.
Okay, I like this play from Dream. I
like it. This is smart. All right, we'll
stay here and if someone else turns up
dead, we know who it is.
>> Just going by myself. I mean, me going
by myself makes me look sus, but I mean,
we don't have mic chat right now.
Hopefully, someone's doing the other
one. Okay, here we go.
>> I'm going to need [music] to win over a
pawn. Nick A30 seems like someone who
would trust me.
>> Okay, here we go.
Oh god, name plate should be back on
now. Is there anyone there?
>> I fixed it. I fixed it.
>> Were you the only one that went?
>> Yeah.
>> So, are you thinking it's Dream as well
or
>> it's Dream or Jimmy's like playing you
guys?
>> We should probably call a meeting in
case someone did die during that. I
mean, Nick is the one that was adamant
he went to the left. Maybe Nick was just
lying and it was Dream the whole time
that went to the left.
>> Well, I mean, maybe maybe he's being
honest. I just think it's [music] it's
so weird. Why would he say that? I was
with him.
>> I 100% can clear Jimmy for that last
round. Okay, so it's probably Dream.
Should we call a button, though?
>> I actually don't think it's you, but
just in case.
>> I called the meeting just to make sure
no one was dead.
>> We were the only ones who fixed this
out, though.
>> Listen, I am telling you, it is Dream
100%.
>> I don't care. I'm going to ruin the
video. I'm I'm going right over there in
the corner. I'm sitting there just to
prove my innocence.
>> I was sus of Jude, okay? He proved to me
in that last round he was [music] not
the killer.
>> Dream, you got someone voted out. I
never saw the kill happen. It's probably
Dream.
>> I WENT LEFT. HE DIDN'T GO LEFT.
>> I know. I know. He went left.
>> It was me and Jimmy and somebody else
went left. Rocks died. Wish Dream Stakes
died. [music] Wish Dream. Dream is
pushing back like he is the imposter. If
he wasn't, he wouldn't care. Let's just
listen to the evidence. Both of them. I
think we know the answer. Like, why are
you fighting so hard, Dream?
>> What do you mean? Why am I FIGHTING SO
HARD? BECAUSE I'M INNOCENT. I'm being
blamed. I want to go sit in the corner.
Skip [music] and let me sit in the
corner.
>> No, no, no, no. You You've gotten too
many people killed. You're dead.
>> What?
>> Yeah, you're dead.
>> Any final words? Who do you think it
might be?
>> I think it's Nick or Jude. So,
>> no shot. It's not you. No shot.
>> Come on. Please.
No shot. What? No. No. No. No. No. No.
No.
>> I'm staying with Sword cuz I know it's
not him.
>> If we stick in groups of two, one person
dies, then we know who the other one is.
We just voted Dream out. But why would
he be lying if he was an imposter? He's
out.
>> That means Nick.
>> Are you lying, Nick?
>> No, no, no. I'm not. I promise. I don't
know. We miscounted or something.
>> Sword. Sword. Come over here.
>> I'm going to do task, guys. I'm going to
do task. Goodbye.
>> I'll go do tasks with you, Nick. I'll go
do tasks.
>> You know, my crazy thing, dude, is you
haven't made any accusation against
anyone else.
>> If I'm not certain of someone, I'm not
going to make an accusation. Right. Come
with me. I have a task.
>> Okay. I I'm going this way. I'm going to
DO MY TASK. NO, DO NOT SEPARATE from me.
>> Okay. Yeah, maybe that's a good point.
Good point. Good point. Okay. Well, the
good news is if if I die with you, then
they know. And I don't think you would
eliminate me if you are the killer right
now because then it's going to be very
obvious it's you.
>> Yeah, actually you're wrong about that
because if I kill you and kill someone
else,
>> then I win if I
>> Oh. Oh, wait. Okay. Should we go and
turn the lights on, Quake?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We should go turn the
lights on because like if Nick kills
Jude right now, once his sword resets,
he kills one of us. Yeah. Then he
instantly wins. Okay, so this is
actually pretty [music] do or die.
>> These guys are so predictable. They're
so easy to manipulate. Come on. [music]
45 51. They're going to be coming over.
They're coming over.
>> I hope they're not on button, though.
>> Well, no. Maybe they're just doing this
to mess with us, but Oh.
Where'd Nick go, guys? No, [screaming]
dude. Don't do it.
Nick's dead and I'm off cool down.
You're not getting to that button.
You're not getting to that button, Mr.
Beast.
>> No, no, no. [screaming]
>> All right, sword. You're dying.
>> NO. NO. [screaming]
NO. NO. Why would you do that? You let
me take Nick away into the loneliest
corner of the map where you would never
find his body. So I killed him right
there and met you guys at lights.
>> I was just telling sword. I know. You
should have sent someone to the button.
I thought you'd know. You let all of
your homies down. You blamed everybody
except for me. Get on the plank. You
were my perfect pawn, Mr. [music] Beast.
>> Dude, don't do this.
>> [music]
>> You tried to trap me. YOU TRIED TO TRAP
ME OUT OF HERE, MR. BEAST. GOODBYE.
>> You can't trap the trapper, Mr. Beast. I
saw what you were doing 3 seconds before
you tried it.
>> Congratulations, Jul. Now, I'm going to
send you the diamond sword. Thank
[music] you for the sword, Mr. Beast.
Let's go. GG's, dude. GG's. If you guys
haven't already, subscribe.